New York State Board of Mediation Cases 5581
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- A 1423 - A 1623 (1941). (Box 9)
  - Ettman, Mitchell, Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Einhorn's Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Five Star Shoe Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Commercial Outfitting Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Accurate Shoe Corp., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Bortolo Bendin, Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Interboro Wrecking Corp., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Sky Chief Radio Corporation, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Premier Sample Card Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Arthur Studios, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Edward Boker, Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Phillips Produce Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Lippert Bros., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Royaltone, Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Atlasko Paper Box Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Decorative Specialty Dyeing Corp., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Michaels Bros., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Spear and Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Spear and Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Consolidated Cork Corp., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Model Paper Box Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Reid and Yeoman, Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Cooper, Louis, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Die casters, Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Hydrox Ice Cream Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Wallach, Frank, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Levine, Sol, Drug Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Aschengrau Bros., Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Joyce Seven-Up Bottling Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - United Cigar-Whelan Stores Corp., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Knickerbocker Village Cooperative Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Formfitting Slipper Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Pocker, Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Mazur and Levy, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Rose Frame and Mirror Works, Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - K and K Market, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Hi-Grade Gas Range and Refrigerator Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Gottlieb, Harry, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Kaplan Brothers, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Grossman, I., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Kono Mfg. Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Raab, Paul, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Zenith Cafeteria, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Coutourier Div. of Industrial Council of Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Wasserman, A., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Mr. Rosenzweig, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - A. Cohen and Sons Corp., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Bell's Dependable Pharmacy, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Gates Container Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Luna Metal Craft Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Britten-Fenton Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - City Provision Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - George Thurm, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Lamparelli, Umberto, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America, Local 16 vs. Food Checkers and Cashiers Union, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - New York Dugan Bros, Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Zella Pharmacy, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Independent Porter Service, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Kew Gardens Window Cleaning Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Smith, E., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - Davega-City Radio, Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 100)
  - Careful Window Cleaning Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Careful Window Cleaning Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 102)
  - Schubach, Alfred, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - N.Y. Dugan Bros Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - United Parcel Service, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - Bloom, M., and Sons Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - Au Canari d'Or, Inc., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 107)
  - Bell Drug Co., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 108)
- A 1802 - A 1863 (1941) (Box 10.1)
  - Bristol Pharmacy, Inc., 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 1)
  - Barry E.J. Inc., 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 2)
  - Wholesale Hardware and House furnishing Assn., Inc., 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 3)
  - Andres, Inc., 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 4)
  - Brach Feld's, 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 5)
  - Sabel, H. and Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 6)
  - True Value Slipper and Sandal Corp., 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 7)
  - Brant Chemists, Inc., 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 8)
  - Clarostat Mfg. Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 9)
  - Spear and Company, 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 10)
  - Socony-Vacuum Oil Co., 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 11)
  - Smith Furniture Exchange, 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 12)
  - Royal Venetian Blind Refinishing Corp., 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 13)
  - Wearbest Footwear, Inc., 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 14)
  - Crystal Manor Inc., 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 15)
  - Elite Specialty Metal Co., 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 16)
  - Brown Bomber Baking Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 17)
  - Richtex Fabrics, 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 18)
  - Standard Baking Co., 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 19)
  - Hamilton Carton Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 20)
  - Valentine and Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 21)
  - North Shore Bus Co., 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 22)
  - Royal Batting and Felting Co., 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 23)
  - Enrich, Henry and Co., 1941 (Box 10.1, Folder 24)
- A 1867 - A 2060 (1941). (Box 11)
  - Continental Baking Co., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Housewreckers, Group of, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Master Bakers, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Card Crafts, Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Bell Drug Co., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Richtex Fabrics, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Borden, Mr., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Pinaud, Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Goodyear Shoe Repairs Stores, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - American Leather Specialties Co., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Schwager and Tobinson, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Salomon, Dr. Samuel, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Becker, Arnold W. Company, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - American Shellac Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Krasne, A., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Stern Bros., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Einhorn Dairy Stores Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - New York Post, Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Field's Shops, Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Schlossman, Samuel and Sons, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Master Watch Case Co., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Automatic Range Co., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - King Mattress Co., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Namm Store, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Hardy Metal Specialties Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Midtown Market, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Slattery Stove Co., J.B., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Goldman-Gershon Sales Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Stark, Mrs. Lillian, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Seiler Furniture Company, Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Garrett and Company, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Rosenbluth Bros., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Delvino Grape Products, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Heileman, Arthur, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - S.N.A. Stationery Co., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Real Kosher Sausage Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Briarcliff Laundry, Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Excavation and Foundation Contractors Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Five Star Shoe Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Waterman and Company, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Taft, Max, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Cluff Fabric Prod. Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Gold Star Venetian Blind Refinishing, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Rosenstock Motors, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Rothstein and Sons, J., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Ludwig Baumann, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Goldman and Ostrow, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Loyal Knit Goods Co., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Claremont Pharmacy, Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Smoked Meat Product Mfrs., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Cohen Co., Paul Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Sunshine Drug Stores, Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Auslander, Abraham, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - McGinnis Restaurant Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Gonzalez, Mario Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - The Rubel Corporation, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Interboro Fuel Company, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Majestic Display Company, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Canergie, Hattie, Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Reid and Yeoman, Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Beacon Shops, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Perfumer's Manufacturing Co., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Stewart's Credit Co., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Sanford Shops, Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Greenbaum, Charles I.H., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Mid-Island Markets, Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Damsky, The Estate of A., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Valentine Paint Co., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - National Casket Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Salomon, Dr. Samuel, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Katz Drug Co., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Glow Realty Corp., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Fagotting Group, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - New York Post, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Childs Company, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Childs Company, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Eveready Hardware Mfg. Co., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Watlow Electric Co., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Feuer, J., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - New York Stationery and Toy Jobbers Association, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Barnett's Express, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Capitol Paint Co., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Quatt and Steiker, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Goldslaug, Mr. Nathan, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Fair Trade and Merchandising Associates, Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Fischer, Mr., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Defiance Button Machine Co., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - White Studio, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Ellas Baking Corp., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Ferber, Morris, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Paramount-Fordham, Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Santore and Sons, Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - Brightman Leather Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Bell, Peter, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Goldfarb, Nathan S., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Iacono, Rosario, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - Microlite Co., Eastern Battery Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Arnold Constable and Co., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - Picadilly Pharmacy, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - Accurate Shoe Corp., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 100)
- A 2068 - A 2282 (1941). (Box 12)
  - Sittner and Bro., N., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Krasne Bros., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Huyler's, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Annette Seigel Millinery, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Arkin Hat Company, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - The Eastern Demolition Co., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - A. Krasne, Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Lilienfeld, Mollye, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Lo Presti Shoe Co., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Manhattan Pontiac Corp., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Mica Products Mfg. Co., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Lew Morris Demolition Co., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Standard Food Products Corp., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - New York Post, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - United Scientific Laboratories, Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Eastern Wine Corp., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Kelly Importing and Distributing Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Greenwood Cemetery, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Elliott Management Corp., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Lehigh Warehouse and Transportation Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Modern Fuel Oil Co. Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Roth and Company, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Herman Cohen and Co., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - New York and Brooklyn Casket Co. Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - The Accurate Shoe Corp., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Rains Foods, Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - The New England Curtain Shop, Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Kiviat, Joe, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Tension Envelope Corp., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Shultz Sample Service, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - March Military Equipment Co. Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Wishen Machine and Tool Workers, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Army and Navy Accessory Store, Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Laboratory Furniture Co., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Marister Management, Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Metro Sacks Co., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Midtown Motor Mart, Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Ansonia Steam Products Co., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Spear and Company, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Ward Baking Company, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Cohen and Lasher, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Interborough New Company, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - John Mullins and Sons, Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Comet Metal Products, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Beyer's Fruit Market, Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Bon-tell Footwear Corp., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Nagle Packing Co. and Others, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Kisseloff, Max, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - May Knitting Company, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Well-worth 5 and 10 Cent Store, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - The Continental Baking Co., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Knickerbocker Photographers, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Empire Hairdressers and Carmen Beauty Salon, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Zuckerbraun Bros., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Rands' Food Shops, Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - State Wrecking Corp., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Fred's Shoe Rebuilding, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Queens-Nassau Transit Lines, Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - The Sixth Hotel Corp., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Radio Wire Television, Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Greenwelk Knitwear Co., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Childs Company, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Max Feinberg, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Ladenheim Fixture Corp., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - E.W. Bliss Company, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - The Avon Wrecking Co., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - The Greater New York Wrecking Corp., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - T.J. Krikorian and Son, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Mazola Bakery, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Artcraft Sample Card Co., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Auerbach and Wilensky, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Oxenberg Bros., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Longwood Parlor Frame Co., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - A.L. Ratner, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Lee Spring Company Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Shultz Sample Service, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - P. Feiner and Sons, Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Callahan's Bakery, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Automatic Woven Wire Supply Co., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - The Weissman Watch Company, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Louis Schachter, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Ideal Cake Company, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Joseph Kleinman, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - A. Goodman and Sons, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - World Steel Products Corp., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - General Baking Company, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Jamaica Buses, Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Queens-Nassau Home Builders League, Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Sam Stein, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - Micamold Radio Corporation, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - School of Mechanical Optics, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 92)
  - Menu Printing Industry (group of employers), 1941 (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - Harry Balinsky, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - Joseph A. Kaplan, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - Ladenheim Fixture Corp., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - Greenwood Cemetery, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - Dobrin Supply Co., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 98)
  - Lynne Pharmacy, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - Fink, Sam, et al., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - William Intner Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - Atlantic Container Corp., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corp., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - Progressive Quilting Co. Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - Coutourier Division of Industrial Council, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - The Putterman Footwear Corp., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - Sidney Siegel, Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 107)
  - 421 West 28th Street Corp., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - Irving Weiner, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 109)
  - Clarostat Manufacturing Co. Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 110)
- A 2283 - A 2554 (1941). (Box 13)
  - Syracuse Milk Dealers, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Bell Sample Card Co., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Roaman's Department Store, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - S. and W. Fine Foods Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - P.A. Trucking, Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Acme Window Display Co., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - March Military Equipment Co., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Max Tillinger, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Novelty Jewelry Mfg. Assn., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Duroyd Gasket and Die Manufacturing, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Sol Geismar, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Alvin Furniture Mfg. Company, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - M. Kamenstein, Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Betty's Millinery, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Gold Star Venetian Blind Refinishing Co., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Lewis Steel Products, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Schekbro Realties, Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Cantilever Shoe Shop, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Perfumers Manufacturing Co., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Smart Millinery Shop, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Valentine and Co. Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Leo Gizer, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Wearbest Footwear, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Service Backing Corp., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Bridge Metal Products, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Marble Industry, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Victor Obler, Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Baltic Shoe Corp., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - B. Monderer, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Sarina Corset Shop, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Dreyfuss Art Company, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Davega-City Radio, Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Highbridge Meat Market, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Kisseloff, Max, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - A. and H. Restaurant, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - E. Feibusch and Company, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Hygrade Products Corp., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Sal's Millinery, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Selikson, Charles, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Zion National Kosher Sausage Factory, Anderson and Tarlow, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Sidney Siegel, Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Levy, Harris, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Cunningham Park Building Corp., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Fashion Mart, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Hugo Brand Tannery Co. Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Sussman-Volk, d/b/a Legold, Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Lord and Burnham Co., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Brite Specialties Company, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Elite Specialty Metal Co., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Service Produce Co., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Bohle Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Barry, E.J., Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Gordon's Department Store, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Kreisler, Jacques Sale Manufacturing Corporation, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Seigel, Alex, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Triboro Coach Corp., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Korral Manufacturing Company, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Industrial Wrecking Company, Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Schieffelin and Company, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Sea Edge Apartments, Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Defiance Button Machine Co., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Empire Curtain Company, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Fitzgerald, Edward P., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - J. Rabinovich, Inc. and Solesto, Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Radio Wire Television, Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Brewster Aeronautical Corp., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Paramount Market, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Lowen's Drug Store, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Upholstery Jobbers Association, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Atlas Sturdy Products Co., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - A. Krasne, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - National Metal-Art Mfg. Company Ic., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Marks C. and S. Shops, Inc.., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Parkchester Review Publishing Co., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Pearl Hat Shop, J'adore Millinery, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Champion Shoe Company, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Amalgamated Housing Corp., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Siegel's Drug Store, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Siegel, Sidney Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Spector Bros., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Wear Best Footwear, Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - 1941 (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - Wellner Motors, Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - Adams Grease Gun Corp., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Colonial Works, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - De Boer and Livingston, Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - General Baking Company, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - Le Roy Metal Bed Company, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - Spear and Company, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Spear and Company, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - Weiser, Herman, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - Marcalus Co., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - Metropolitan Displaymen's Assn, Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - Williams, James B. Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - Enrich, Henry A. and Company, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - 886 Fairmount Place, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - Manufacturers Machine and Tool Co., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 98)
  - Mercury Management Corp., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 99)
  - Wolin and Ross, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - McQuade and Company, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 101)
  - Purs, John G., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 102)
  - Sudnow and Kaufman, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 103)
  - Decorative Cabinet Corp., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 104)
  - Fischer, J.P. Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 105)
  - G.G. Precision Works, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 106)
  - Hotel Diplomat, Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 107)
  - Jassem, Hyman Company, Inc., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 108)
  - Lipsett Wrecking and Salvage Corp., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - Mazur Bros., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 110)
- A 2561 - A 2768 (1942). (Box 14)
  - Weil and Company, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Watchcase Manufacturers, Board of Trade, Inc., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Daylight Baking Company, Inc., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Breakstone Bros., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Transformer Corp. of America, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Gottfried Baking Company: Vonie, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Cooper Pharmacy, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Finkenberg's, A. and Sons, Inc., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Long Beach Bus Company, Inc., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Ludwig Baumann and Company, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Siegel Drug, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Monderer, Bernard, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Admiration Products, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Elkind Construction Company, Inc., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - European Radio Company, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Fitzgerald, Edward P., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Metro Sacks Company, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Oxman, William, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Annello's, Carmello Bakery Shop, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Arnold Constable and Co., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Sosnow, M. Inc., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - American Jewish Congress, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Cohen, J. and K. Furniture Company, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Lenox Road Realty Co. Inc., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - North Shore Bus Co. Inc., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Childs Company, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Enrich, Henry A. and Co., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Helen's Bakery, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Atlantic Machinery Company, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Hascom Baking Corp., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Munchick, Philip, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Mica Products, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Gottfried Furniture Co., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 33)